,website,url,headline,entities
0,CNN,https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-14-20-intl/index.html,What you need to know,[]
1,CNN,https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-14-20-intl/index.html,Inside the multibillion dollar vaccine race,"[('multibillion dollar', 'MONEY')]"
2,CNN,https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-14-20-intl/index.html,New Zealand extends coronavirus restrictions for 12 more days,"[('New Zealand', 'GPE'), ('12 more days', 'DATE')]"
3,CNN,https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-14-20-intl/index.html,"United States reports more than 51,000 coronavirus cases","[('United States', 'GPE'), ('more than 51,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
4,CNN,https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-14-20-intl/index.html,It's almost 6.30 p.m. in Wellington and 9.30 a.m. in Moscow. Here's the latest on the coronavirus pandemic,"[('almost 6.30 p.m.', 'TIME'), ('Wellington', 'GPE'), ('9.30 a.m.', 'TIME'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
5,CNN,https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-14-20-intl/index.html,"Doctor deaths from Covid-19 in India have reached ""alarming"" levels, Indian Medical Association says","[('India', 'GPE'), ('Indian Medical Association', 'ORG')]"
6,CNN,https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-14-20-intl/index.html,President Bolsonaro says Brazil is in better economic shape than most other countries amid Covid-19,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
7,CNN,https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-14-20-intl/index.html,India announces air corridor with Maldives to bolster tourism,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Maldives', 'GPE')]"
8,CNN,https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-14-20-intl/index.html,"India reports more than 64,500 coronavirus cases","[('India', 'GPE'), ('more than 64,500', 'CARDINAL')]"
9,CNN,https://edition.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-pandemic-08-14-20-intl/index.html,South Korea sees over 100 new coronavirus cases for first time since April,"[('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('over 100', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('April', 'DATE')]"
10,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Record U.S. coronavirus fatalities and 'startling surge' of cases in children and teens,"[('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
11,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Trump's tweet about college football is the epitome of COVID-19 irony. Here's why.,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
12,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,House Democrats demand Postal Service chief roll back changes ahead of Election Day,"[('House', 'ORG'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Postal Service', 'ORG'), ('Election Day', 'DATE')]"
13,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"California passes 600,000 coronavirus cases","[('California', 'GPE'), ('600,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
14,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"3-year-old with autism and family kicked off Southwest flight over mask, mother says","[('Southwest', 'LOC')]"
15,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,California parents sue Gov. Gavin Newsom to open schools for in-person learning,"[('California', 'GPE'), ('Gavin Newsom', 'PERSON')]"
16,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Coronavirus threatens the survival of indigenous Colombians,"[('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('Colombians', 'NORP')]"
17,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,They were already struggling. Then they were hit by cash lenders' 'gangster' tactics.,[]
18,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Georgia high school closed due to coronavirus in district with 1K in quarantine,"[('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('1K', 'QUANTITY')]"
19,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Dallas Cowboys owner Jerry Jones expects fans to attend home games,"[('Dallas', 'GPE'), ('Jerry Jones', 'PERSON')]"
20,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Landlords could exploit COVID-19 victims to fast-track evictions, housing advocates say",[]
21,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,These viral COVID-19 mask 'exemptions' are legally — and morally — indefensible,[]
22,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Trump's COVID-19 proxy Dr. Birx reveals danger of putting career over country,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Birx', 'PERSON')]"
23,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,I'm an ER doctor. Here's a troubling reason patients ignore COVID-19 advice.,[]
24,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,COVID-19 stimulus standoff is an opportunity to undo Trumpian damage. Here's how.,"[('Trumpian', 'NORP')]"
25,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,How the pandemic could force schools in California — and beyond — to rethink education,"[('California', 'GPE')]"
26,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,A look at the back-to-school debate through a teacher’s eyes,[]
27,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Mom, teacher, lunch buddy: Parents gear up for a virtual start to the school year","[('the school year', 'DATE')]"
28,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,California mayor says it's time to rethink living wages in America,"[('California', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
29,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,People with disabilities are more at risk during pandemic. Here’s how they’re dealing with it.,[]
30,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"The complicated balancing act of church, state and the coronavirus ",[]
31,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Does air conditioning spread the coronavirus?,[]
32,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Trump blames testing for spike in COVID-19 cases. Experts disagree. ,[]
33,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Is this the second wave of COVID-19 in the U.S.? Or are we still in the first?,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
34,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Trump falsely claims coronavirus numbers are 'going down almost everywhere',"[('Trump', 'PRODUCT')]"
35,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,What you need to know about coronavirus home-testing kits,[]
36,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Doctors, nurses and hospital staff",[]
37,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Small businesses and their employees,[]
38,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Senior citizens and the elderly,[]
39,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,What cleaning products kill the coronavirus?,[]
40,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Are at-home testing kits available?,[]
41,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Can you catch COVID-19 twice? ,[]
42,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Gyms are eager to reopen, but are they safe?",[]
43,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,How will coronavirus change the way we fly?,[]
44,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Covid Chronicles, Vol. 6: Virus testing becomes a test of character","[('Covid Chronicles', 'PERSON'), ('Vol', 'GPE'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Virus', 'ORG')]"
45,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,It's been months since the first U.S. coronavirus death. Here's a look at some of the lives lost.,"[('months', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
46,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Affairs, hoarders and hope: Read anonymous confessions in the time of the coronavirus",[]
47,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Millions are now out of work. Many wonder if there will be a job to go back to.,"[('Millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
48,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,MSNBC Special Report: Testing and the Road to Reopening,"[('MSNBC', 'ORG')]"
49,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,'Into The Red Zone': An NBC News NOW documentary ,"[(""The Red Zone'"", 'ORG'), ('NBC News', 'ORG')]"
50,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,These stunning images show life—even amid the pandemic. The sprawling exhibit is in the streets.,[]
51,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Portrait of a neighborhood under lockdown,[]
52,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Photos capture empty cities across the globe,[]
53,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,New Yorkers are giving nightly ovations to health workers. These are their portraits,"[('New Yorkers', 'NORP')]"
54,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,In case you missed it,[]
55,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,These states have the most coronavirus cases. See the day-by-day breakdown.,[]
56,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,CDC: Avoid masks with valves to stop the spread of the coronavirus,"[('CDC', 'ORG')]"
57,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"AMC to open 100 theaters next week, majority of locations in early September","[('AMC', 'ORG'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('next week', 'DATE'), ('early September', 'DATE')]"
58,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Kentucky governor pleads with schools to delay in-person instruction,"[('Kentucky', 'GPE')]"
59,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Coronavirus found on imported frozen food packaging in 3 Chinese cities,"[('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
60,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"Florida sheriff orders deputies not to wear masks, bans civilians in masks from office","[('Florida', 'GPE')]"
61,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Texas is 'flying blind' as schools reopen amid decline in COVID-19 testing,"[('Texas', 'GPE')]"
62,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,DeVos publicly absent as critical decisions are made on public school reopenings,[]
63,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,Video shows man's anti-mask tirade in Arizona store before he is hauled out,"[('Arizona', 'GPE')]"
64,NBC,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,"'No masks, no social distancing': 2 men charged after large pool party in N.J., police say","[('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('N.J.', 'GPE')]"
65,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Latest news for health care. ,[]
66,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Most scientists think 60% to 80% of the population needs to be vaccinated or have natural antibodies to achieve herd immunity.,"[('60% to 80%', 'PERCENT')]"
67,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,President Donald Trump on Thursday rejected former Vice President Joe Biden's call for a national mask mandate to combat the coronavirus.,"[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON')]"
68,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"""Some have called this Russian roulette,"" NIH Director Dr. Francis Collins said.","[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('NIH', 'ORG'), ('Francis Collins', 'PERSON')]"
69,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"U.S. public health officials are beginning to see a ""disturbing"" uptick in the rate of coronavirus tests that come back positive in some regions of the nation, Fauci said.","[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Fauci', 'ORG')]"
70,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"Epic has now notified staff that they can work from home until the end of 2020. Earlier this week, it said it had paused its plan requiring thousands of employees to return to offices this month.","[('the end of 2020', 'DATE'), ('Earlier this week', 'DATE'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('this month', 'DATE')]"
71,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,WHO Director-General Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus said that the development of vaccines is risky and some may fail. He said spreading the investment in vaccine development among different countries shares the risk of failure and the reward of success.,"[('Adhanom Ghebreyesus', 'ORG')]"
72,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"The coronavirus is at least as deadly as the 1918 flu pandemic and the death toll could even be worse if world leaders and public health officials fail to adequately contain it, researchers say.","[('1918', 'DATE')]"
73,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,World Health Organization officials are holding a press conference on Thursday to update the public on the coronavirus outbreak that has infected more than 20 million people across the globe.,"[('World Health Organization', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('more than 20 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
74,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,The S&P 500 will attempt to reclaim its record high hit before the coronavirus pandemic.,[]
75,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"Critics of Sweden's controversial coronavirus strategy have called on the country's health officials to put measures in place to prepare for, and prevent, a potential second wave of the virus in the fall.","[('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('the fall', 'DATE')]"
76,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"The coronavirus has infected more than 20.7 million people around the world as of Thursday, killing at least 751,400 people. ","[('more than 20.7 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('at least 751,400', 'CARDINAL')]"
77,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Kroger and CVS Health are both pitching Covid-19 testing programs to employers to help them reopen and operate safely as the pandemic continues.,"[('Kroger', 'ORG'), ('CVS Health', 'ORG')]"
78,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Duterte had earlier this week volunteered to participate in trials for the Russian vaccine even as scientists and health experts questioned the safety and effectiveness of the drug.,"[('Duterte', 'ORG'), ('earlier this week', 'DATE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
79,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,President Donald Trump said the federal government is sending 125 million reusable face masks to school districts across the United States as schools consider whether it's safe to reopen this fall amid the coronavirus pandemic.,"[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('125 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('this fall', 'DATE')]"
80,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Democratic vice presidential pick Sen. Kamala Harris blamed President Donald Trump for the severity of the coronavirus outbreak in the United States.,"[('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
81,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"In Texas, new Covid-19 cases have fallen by 10% to an average of 7,381 a day from 8,203 two weeks ago, but testing is down by 53% over the same time.","[('Texas', 'GPE'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('7,381', 'CARDINAL'), ('8,203', 'CARDINAL'), ('two weeks ago', 'DATE'), ('53%', 'PERCENT')]"
82,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Louis enrolled in the Phase 3 Moderna coronavirus vaccine trial at a site in Las Vegas. Here's what it was like.,"[('Louis', 'PERSON'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Moderna', 'NORP'), ('Las Vegas', 'GPE')]"
83,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Joe Biden's pick of Sen. Kamala Harris of California as his running mate brings him a powerful ally in the fight against the coronavirus if the Democratic slate wins the 2020 presidential election.,"[(""Joe Biden's"", 'PERSON'), ('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('California', 'GPE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('2020', 'CARDINAL')]"
84,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"On Tuesday, Russia announced that it had registered a coronavirus vaccine, making it the first country to do so.","[('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
85,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,U.S. stock futures rose sharply on Wednesday as traders tried to recover from a tech-led pullback in the previous session.,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE')]"
86,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"The coronavirus has infected more than 20.4 million people around the world as of Thursday, killing at least 745,923 people. ","[('more than 20.4 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('at least 745,923', 'CARDINAL')]"
87,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"Russia has rejected international criticism and skepticism toward its coronavirus vaccine, saying that it's safe and that it works.","[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
88,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,The U.K. economy contracted by 20.4% in the second quarter of 2020 as coronavirus-induced lockdowns hammered activity.,"[('U.K.', 'GPE'), ('20.4%', 'PERCENT'), ('the second quarter of 2020', 'DATE')]"
89,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"J. Stephen Morrison of the Center for Strategic and International Studies said Russian President Vladimir Putin is trying to score ""a domestic win"" with the planned rollout of Russia's vaccine.","[('J. Stephen Morrison', 'PERSON'), ('the Center for Strategic and International Studies', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Vladimir Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
90,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Moderna separately said the deal for its vaccine is worth $1.53 billion and will give the federal government the option to purchase up to 400 million additional doses.,"[('Moderna', 'GPE'), ('$1.53 billion', 'MONEY'), ('up to 400 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
91,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"""Being a 21-year-old, I should not be spending six days in the hospital for lung complications,"" said one young vaper who survived coronavirus.","[('six days', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
92,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"The trial was supposed to start this year, but was delayed due to the coronavirus pandemic.","[('this year', 'DATE')]"
93,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,"Florida is one of the states hit hardest by the coronavirus, but daily new cases have appeared to decline in recent days. Testing, however, has fallen even faster.","[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('recent days', 'DATE')]"
94,CNBC,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,Alphabet's Verily has built its own lab focused on Covid-19 testing. Verily said it can run several thousand tests per day,"[('Alphabet', 'GPE'), ('Verily', 'GPE'), ('Verily', 'PERSON'), ('several thousand', 'CARDINAL')]"
95,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,"Englishहिन्दीमराठीবাংলা ગુજરાતીಕನ್ನಡதமிழ்తెలుగుമലയാളം|Epaper|GadgetsNowSign InTOITOICoronavirusBriefsWorldBusinessSportsEntertainmentTVLifestylePhotosEducationPoliticsElectionsCoronavirusHas curve flattened?India Lockdown: FAQsPreventionTreatmentSymptomsIndiaDelhiBangaloreHyderabadKolkataMumbaiWorldCovid-19 FAQsSpeaking TreeNews HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCouponsNewsCoronaviruscovid-19 casesIndiaWorldview on mapSource: MOHFW(India) and John HopkinsDailyCumulative.css-2b097c-container{position:relative;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-8rldbw-control{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;background-color:hsl(0,0%,100%);border-color:hsl(0,0%,80%);border-radius:0px;border-style:solid;border-width:0;cursor:default;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex-wrap:wrap;-ms-flex-wrap:wrap;flex-wrap:wrap;-webkit-box-pack:justify;-webkit-justify-content:space-between;-ms-flex-pack:justify;justify-content:space-between;min-height:38px;outline:0 !important;position:relative;-webkit-transition:all 100ms;transition:all 100ms;box-sizing:border-box;border-bottom:1px solid #000;font-size:16px;font-weight:600;}.css-8rldbw-control:hover{border-color:hsl(0,0%,70%);}.css-1hwfws3{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex:1;-ms-flex:1;flex:1;-webkit-flex-wrap:wrap;-ms-flex-wrap:wrap;flex-wrap:wrap;padding:2px 8px;-webkit-overflow-scrolling:touch;position:relative;overflow:hidden;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-12jugfk-placeholder{color:#999;margin-left:2px;margin-right:2px;position:absolute;top:50%;-webkit-transform:translateY(-50%);-ms-transform:translateY(-50%);transform:translateY(-50%);box-sizing:border-box;font-size:14px;font-weight:600;}Select State/UT.css-1g6gooi{margin:2px;padding-bottom:2px;padding-top:2px;visibility:visible;color:hsl(0,0%,20%);box-sizing:border-box;}.css-1wy0on6{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-align-self:stretch;-ms-flex-item-align:stretch;align-self:stretch;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex-shrink:0;-ms-flex-negative:0;flex-shrink:0;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-43ykx9-indicatorSeparator{-webkit-align-self:stretch;-ms-flex-item-align:stretch;align-self:stretch;background-color:hsl(0,0%,80%);margin-bottom:8px;margin-top:8px;width:1px;box-sizing:border-box;display:none;}.css-h0ri03-indicatorContainer{color:hsl(0,0%,80%);display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;padding:8px;-webkit-transition:color 150ms;transition:color 150ms;box-sizing:border-box;background-image:url(https://static.toiimg.com/photo/74612995.cms);background-repeat:no-repeat;background-position:-13px -227px;}.css-h0ri03-indicatorContainer:hover{color:hsl(0,0%,60%);}.css-19bqh2r{display:inline-block;fill:currentColor;line-height:1;stroke:currentColor;stroke-width:0;}Has the curve flattened?Find OutCovid-19 India StatusBy State/UTBy DistrictPreventive MeasuresPrecautions we suggest: Wash hands frequently, avoid crowded places...read moreCoronavirus SymptomsIf you have a fever, cough and difficulty breathing...read moreMyths vs RealityBe aware! The most pervasive myths on Coronavirus and why they are wrong.read moreLive Updates Coronavirus live updates: India's Covid tally now over 24 lakh, deaths cross 48,000-markQ&A ON CORONAVIRUS (COVID-19) #CautionYesPanicNoWith inputs from:How is one tested for Covid-19?The test for coronavirus does not involve any blood examination. Coronavirus test includes examining of the throat swab or the nasal swab to check for infection. After taking samples, doctors posted at nodal hospitals may assess your physical health to decide whether hospitalisation is needed. Otherwise, you may be asked to stay isolated at home itself. If the tests are positive, you may require to remain quarantined for at least 14 days, till recovery.What should you do if you want to get tested for Covid-19 in India?If you get infected with COVID-19 and recover, can you get infected again?Can higher immunity prevent you from getting coronavirus?Should I wear a mask?more questions and answersTesting CentresCollection CentresFind COVID-19 testing centres near you.css-2b097c-container{position:relative;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-8rldbw-control{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;background-color:hsl(0,0%,100%);border-color:hsl(0,0%,80%);border-radius:0px;border-style:solid;border-width:0;cursor:default;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex-wrap:wrap;-ms-flex-wrap:wrap;flex-wrap:wrap;-webkit-box-pack:justify;-webkit-justify-content:space-between;-ms-flex-pack:justify;justify-content:space-between;min-height:38px;outline:0 !important;position:relative;-webkit-transition:all 100ms;transition:all 100ms;box-sizing:border-box;border-bottom:1px solid #000;font-size:16px;font-weight:600;}.css-8rldbw-control:hover{border-color:hsl(0,0%,70%);}.css-1hwfws3{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex:1;-ms-flex:1;flex:1;-webkit-flex-wrap:wrap;-ms-flex-wrap:wrap;flex-wrap:wrap;padding:2px 8px;-webkit-overflow-scrolling:touch;position:relative;overflow:hidden;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-1wh03ml-singleValue{color:#000;margin-left:2px;margin-right:2px;max-width:calc(100% - 8px);overflow:hidden;position:absolute;text-overflow:ellipsis;white-space:nowrap;top:50%;-webkit-transform:translateY(-50%);-ms-transform:translateY(-50%);transform:translateY(-50%);box-sizing:border-box;}Delhi.css-1g6gooi{margin:2px;padding-bottom:2px;padding-top:2px;visibility:visible;color:hsl(0,0%,20%);box-sizing:border-box;}.css-1wy0on6{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-align-self:stretch;-ms-flex-item-align:stretch;align-self:stretch;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex-shrink:0;-ms-flex-negative:0;flex-shrink:0;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-43ykx9-indicatorSeparator{-webkit-align-self:stretch;-ms-flex-item-align:stretch;align-self:stretch;background-color:hsl(0,0%,80%);margin-bottom:8px;margin-top:8px;width:1px;box-sizing:border-box;display:none;}.css-h0ri03-indicatorContainer{color:hsl(0,0%,80%);display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;padding:8px;-webkit-transition:color 150ms;transition:color 150ms;box-sizing:border-box;background-image:url(https://static.toiimg.com/photo/74612995.cms);background-repeat:no-repeat;background-position:-13px -227px;}.css-h0ri03-indicatorContainer:hover{color:hsl(0,0%,60%);}.css-19bqh2r{display:inline-block;fill:currentColor;line-height:1;stroke:currentColor;stroke-width:0;}All India Institute of Medical Sciences, New Delhi- 110029Lady Hardinge Medical College, New DelhiLal Path Labs, Block -E, Sector 18, Rohini, DelhiDr Dangs Lab, C-2/1, Safadarjung Development Area, New-DelhiLaboratory Services, Indraprastha Apollo Hospitals, Sarita Vihar, New Delhi Max Lab, Max Super Speciality Hospital, Saket, New-DelhiSir Ganga Ram Hospital Clinical Lab Services, Sir Ganga Ram Hospital, DelhiOncquest Labs Ltd, 3-Factory Road, New-DelhiPrognosis Laboratories, 515-16, Sector 19, DwarkaCity X-Ray & Scan Clinic Pvt Ltd, 4B/18, Tilak Nagar, New DelhiNational Centre for Disease ControlRam Manohar Lohia HospitalInstitute of Liver & Biliary SciencesArmy Hospital Research & ReferralNote: No. of testing labs and collection centres are increasing. We will keep updating it as and when we get more information.Quick TipsLockdown: What's open?know moreHow to Self Quarantine?know moreDo's and Dont's for Covid-19know moreCovid-19 or flu? How to find out?know moreMost Rampant Myths on Covid-19 #CautionYesPanicNoSpraying alcohol or chlorine all over your body kill the coronavirusEating garlic can treat coronavirusCold weather and snow kill the new coronavirusTaking a hot bath prevents the new coronavirus diseaseThe new coronavirus can be transmitted through a mosquito biteHand dryers are effective in killing the new coronavirusPets at home can spread the new coronavirusThe virus only affects older peopleread full listGovernment Advisory Advisory - Social DistancingDirectives from MoHRD for all Educational Institutions and Examination Boards regarding precautions to be taken in light of COVID-19DoPT OM - Preventive measures to be taken to contain the spread of Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19)Latest Testing Guidelines of Indian Council of Medical Research (ICMR)Guidelines for notifying COVID-19 affected persons by Private InstitutionsStandard Operating Procedure for Passenger Movement post DisembarkationLatest News from CoronavirusIndiaOver 64,000 fresh Covid-19 cases; recovery rate improves to 71.17%India's Covid-19 caseload surpassed 24 lakh on Friday after 64,553 people tested positive in a day, and the recoveries rose to over 17 lakh, the health ministry said. With 17,51,555 people defeating the disease, the recovery rate has surged to 71.17 per cent. The caseload increased to 24,61,190, while the death toll climbed to 48,040 with 1,007 people succumbing to the disease in 24 hours, the ministry data updated at 8 am showed.US, China to discuss trade deal amid Covid-19 disruptionZydus' 'budget' injection costs 2,800/shotCentre distributed 3cr masks, 1.2cr PPEsIn biggest Covid surge, 66,000+ cases, 1,008 deaths in one dayWHO chief scientist bats for focus on contact tracing, testing in fight against Covid-19Russia not world's first to develop coronavirus vaccine: Kiran Mazumdar-ShawCoronavirus curve 'frightening, not flattening': Rahul GandhiCoronavirus roundup: Developments in India and rest of worldMSN Labs rolls out cheapest Covid-19 drug FavipiravirBio E in pact with J&J to manufacture Covid-19 vaccineDelhi956 new Covid-19 cases take Delhi tally to 1,49,460; death toll climbs to 4,167Delhi recorded 956 fresh coronavirus cases on Thursday, raising the city's infection tally to over 1.49 lakh, while the death toll from the disease mounted to 4,167, authorities said.1,113 more Covid-19 cases in Delhi; 14 more deaths1,300 new cases take Delhi's Covid-19 caseload to over 1.45 lakh; toll climbs to 4,111Covid-19 situation in Delhi under control: Arvind Kejriwal613 new Covid-19 cases in Delhi; toll 3853Delhi records 1,075 fresh Covid-19 cases; tally rises to 1,30,606: AuthoritiesCovid-19 'situation satisfactory' in Delhi: Satyendra JainPeople, govts together attained victory over Covid-19, fight not yet over: Arvind KejriwalDelhi unlock 2.0 news: Today's updatesRecovered Delhi cop tests positive again, raises question if coronavirus can reinfectDelhi govt plans more monthly sero-surveys, next to be done in August: Satyendar JainBangaloreTotal number of Covid-19 infections breach 2 lakh-mark in KarnatakaThe number of Covid-19 infections breached the 2 lakh mark in Karnataka on Thursday as the state reported 6,706 new cases of coronavirus and 103 related fatalities, taking the death toll to 3,613.Karnataka: Siddaramaiah discharged after testing negative for Covid-19Over one lakh Covid patients discharged so far in Karnataka, 6,257 new infectionsPrompt hospital admission after positive antigen test: BBMPCovid-19: Health teams to test vulnerable citizens across KarnatakaBengaluru: Volunteer group serves food to city Covid doctorsWith BS Yediyurappa in hospital, cabinet reshuffle, policies hang fireFormer Karnataka CM Siddaramaiah tests positive for Covid, admitted to hospitalBiggest single-day spike of 6,128 new Covid-19 cases in KarnatakaKarnataka forest minister tests positive for Covid-19Bengaluru: Collective effort helped Yelahanka apartment stay safeHyderabadHyderabad: Cop donates plasma for Covid-positive doctor, who treated 300 coronavirus patientsConstable E Vijay Kumar from Chilkalguda police station in Hyderabad, who contracted coronavirus in June this year while performing his duties as front-line worker at Gandhi General Hospital, on Thursday donated his plasma to save the life of a senior doctor, who has treated at least 300 Covid-19 patients, before he himself contracted the infection.Health minister inaugurates special buses for Covid monitoringTelangana CM directs release of prisoners with good conduct on occasion of Independence DayCovid-19: Telangana toll tops 400-mark , state records 1,478 new infectionsTelangana: Villagers protest burial of Covid victim RMP doctorPeople make a beeline for free Covid-19 test at Secunderabad Cantt BoardCO Helper App to provide info on Covid-19 beds, ambulancesCovid-19: Greater Hyderabad Municipal Corporation redefines containment zonesTech Mahindra charters flight to bring 210 staffers, kin in US homeHyderabad: Janapriya Nile association gets its act together to fight Covid-19Telangana registers 9 Covid-19 deaths, 1,550 new infectionsKolkataWest Bengal govt withdraws state-wide lockdown on August 28The Mamata Banerjee-led West Bengal government on Wednesday withdrew the complete lockdown on August 28 and imposed a curfew on August 20 instead.Traffic cop succumbs to Covid-19 in KolkataAnother senior doctor dies of Covid-19 in KolkataWest Bengal reports 40 new Covid-19 deaths, 2,341 fresh casesKolkata police sensitise people about bi-weekly lockdownWest Bengal tourism department reopens 10 facilities amid Covid-19 pandemicSeven-day lockdown imposed from 5pm in all containment zones of West BengalCovid-19 claims 16 more lives in West Bengal; 649 fresh casesMamata Banerjee extends free ration scheme of West Bengal govt till June 2021Commuter hassles aggravate in Kolkata as several private buses stay off roads citing lossesWest Bengal reports highest single-day spike of 572 Covid-19 cases; tally crosses 17,000-markMumbaiMaharashtra: 11,813 new Covid cases, 413 deaths, 9,115 recoveriesMaharashtra registered a spike of 11,813 new cases on Thursday which took the coronavirus tally in the state to 5,60,126. With 413 Covid-19 patients dying, the death toll in the state reached 19,063, the state health department said.Mumbai reports 925 new Covid-19 cases, 46 more dieUnlock 3.0 in Mumbai: Coronavirus cases update and latest news from your cityVandalism at BR Ambedkar's Mumbai house: Two suspects test positive for Covid-19Mumbai reports 1,033 new Covid-19 cases, 39 deathsMaharashtra reports 7,924 fresh Covid-19 cases, 227 deathsMumbai: Dharavi adds 9 new Covid-19 cases; doubling rate over 238 days1,115 new Covid-19 cases detected in Mumbai; 57 more dieMaharashtra's Covid-19 count grows by 9,431; death toll now 13,656I'm not ready to let people die by lifting lockdown in one go: Uddhav ThackerayMumbai: Dharavi reports 36 new Covid-19 casesRest of the WorldNew low-cost test can diagnose Covid-19 in just 20 minutesMELBOURNE: Scientists have developed a new low-cost nasal swab test which can accurately diagnose the presence of SARS-CoV-2 virus that causes Covid-19 in just 20 minutes.WHO in conversation with Russia for more vaccine information: expertIndonesia takes part in late-stage China vaccine trialNew Zealand probing for outbreak source, may expand lockdownBiological E to make substance used in J&J's potential Covid-19 vaccineUS recruits scientists abroad for Covid-19 vaccine trials, pledges access to supplyUK begins testing a new app to fight Covid-19 spreadFinland reverses policy, recommends mask useScientists identify hundreds of drugs to treat Covid-19Germany: Optimistic we'll have a vaccine in coming months and certainly next yearPhilippines eyes clinical trials for Russian Covid-19 vaccine in OctoberSpeaking Tree StoriesChronicle of a pandemic foretoldPerhaps one of the earliest fictional accounts of a global threat that wipes out all forms of life is Arthur Conan Doyle’s The Poison Belt, which features the scientific genius, Professor Challenger, and was written in 1913.How to connect despite physical distancingIs your cough infectious?New doorway to introspectionCorona Karma?Corona is here, but where is karuna?Fearlessness  and ahimsaWe’re part of the wholeTake this quiz and see how you fareShh be still, be calmProtect yourself from the fear contagion Video updates on Coronavirus 01:13Spraying disinfectants on streets can be 'harmful': WHO01:13Spraying disinfectants on streets can be 'harmful': WHO01:35Indore: Migrant workers, stranded students sent to Rewa by special train01:03Noida: 3,000 migrant workers travel to Bihar onboard special trains01:54Heartwarming messages from stranded Indians as they board repatriation flight from Dhaka01:52Rural Health Pharmacies employees protest over salary hike in Punjab01:32Govt rubbishes privacy concerns in Aarogya Setu, says app designed with ‘privacy-first’ measure01:194,213 COVID-19 cases in last 24 hours, recovery rate improved to 31.15%: Centre01:104000 Indians brought back by flights, 5 lakh migrants went home via trains: Centre03:23COVID-19: GCC Biotech lab prepares ‘real-time’ test kits worth Rs 500 in WB01:07Lockdown 3.0: Standalone outlets reopen in ChennaiMore Updates from CoronavirusLive: Biggest single-day spike of 49,310 casesIndia, Israel to develop rapid testing for CovidCan you get Covid again? It’s unlikely, experts say  Covid-19 roundup: Developments in India & worldIndia needs one million tests daily: CCMB chiefCM Arvind Kejriwal rules out another lockdownCoronavirus vaccine update: All you need to knowLive: Signs of economic recovery visible, says PMICMR nod for antigen-based testing kit for faster diagnosis6,300+ new Covid cases, nearly 3k from MahaCovid: Economist warns of 10 yrs of depression‘Lockdown prevented 37,000-78,000 deaths’Covid live: Total cases in India rise to 1,25,101Covid-19: Home loan rates set to dip, EMIs to fallIndia records over 5,200 Covid cases in a dayCovid-19: India reports 0.2 deaths per lakhDental clinics: Only urgent cases allowedWHO faces virus probe after Trump ultimatum'Migrants to be tracked, focus on keeping toll low'Railways to run 200 non-AC trains daily from June 1The first case of coronavirus was reported in December 2019 in the Wuhan city of China as a pneumonia outbreak. Later, its root was traced to a novel strain of coronavirus. The outbreak of coronavirus infection soon spread to other provinces of the country, forcing the govt to lockdown dozen of cities with millions of people. Within weeks, the coronavirus spread outside of the country to other nations like South Korea, Iran, Italy, United States, India, Pakistan among others.  The number of positive cases of novel coronavirus infection is increasing day-by-day all across the globe. Countries around the world have taken strict decisions to close the entry of foreigners, schools, colleges, gyms, clubs, cinema halls, malls and other public places to stop the spread of Covid-19. The novel coronavirus also knocked down the global financial markets with billions of dollars being wiped off in a matter of a few weeks.Get the appback to topOther Times Group news sitesThe Economic TimesHindi Economic TimesNavbharat TimesMaharashtra TimesVijaya KarnatakaTelugu SamayamTamil SamayamMalayalam SamayamEi SamayI am GujaratTimes NowTimes Now HindiTimesPointsIndiatimesBrand CapitalEducation TimesTimes FoodMiss KyraMumbai MirrorPune MirrorAhmedabad MirrorBangalore MirrorMX PlayerNBT Gold PodcastEi Samay Gold PodcastMX ShareKaroMX TakaTak AppLiving and entertainmentMensXP.comFeminaETimesGraziaZoomTravel DestinationsBombay TimesCricbuzz.comFilmfareOnline SongsTVLifestyle Longwalks AppNewspaper SubscriptionFood NewsTimes PrimeWhats Hottop trendsCoronavirus cases in IndiaKamala HarrisPranab MukherjeeCoronavirus India update liveSachin PilotPranab Mukherjee newsRajasthan newsRetail InflationFinal Year Exam NewsCBSE Compartment ExamH1B VisaComedk Exam NewsNewsFinal Year Exam NewsCoronavirus newsHoroscope todayLatest newsStep by Step Pizza RecipeservicesAds 2 BookBank Exam AppET Money Finance AppCouponDuniaDineoutMagicbricksTechgigTimes JobsBollywood NewsTimes MobileRemit 2 IndiaTC NextAstro SpeakGadgets NowCareersColombiaPopular CategoriesHeadlinesSports NewsBusiness NewsIndia NewsWorld NewsBollywood NewsHealth & Fitness TipsIndian TV ShowsCelebrity Photoshot on the webKareena Kapoor KhanSSR CaseSSR Case Live UpdatesSSR Former ManagerSanjay DuttSSR NieceSushant SisterAlia BhattSanjana SanghiTrending topicsDisha PataniBollywood CelebsNiharika KonidelaMouni RoyCentre on SSR CaseVijay FanShweta Video AppealIbrahim Ali KhanSanjay Dutt's CousinSushant FamilyKareena KapoorOxford Coronavirus VaccineAmazon App QuizJio Janmashtami OfferMoto Razr 5G 2020Vivo Y1sAmazon SaleCoronavirus in MumbaiFollow us onfacebooktwitterrss feedyoutubedownload toi appandroidiphoneBlackBerryipadwindows phoneText resize:aaaAbout us Create Your Own Ad Terms of Use and Grievance Redressal Policy Privacy policy Advertise with us RSS Sitemap Archives Copyright © 2020 Bennett, Coleman & Co. Ltd. All rights reserved. For reprint rights: Times Syndication Service","[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG'), ('EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe', 'PRODUCT'), ('mapSource', 'ORG'), ('John HopkinsDailyCumulative.css-2b097c-container{position', 'PERSON'), ('relative;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;background', 'CARDINAL'), ('flexbox;display', 'CARDINAL'), ('wrap;flex', 'CARDINAL'), ('important;position', 'CARDINAL'), ('relative;-webkit', 'ORG'), ('100ms;transition', 'CARDINAL'), ('100ms;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('#000;font', 'MONEY'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('flex;-webkit-flex:1;-ms', 'PRODUCT'), ('wrap;-ms-flex-wrap', 'PRODUCT'), ('wrap;flex', 'CARDINAL'), ('touch;position', 'CARDINAL'), ('relative;overflow', 'CARDINAL'), ('hidden;box', 'GPE'), ('translateY(-50%);-ms', 'PERSON'), ('translateY(-50%);box', 'PRODUCT'), ('visible;color', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('flexbox;display', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;background', 'CARDINAL'), ('150ms;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('DistrictPreventive MeasuresPrecautions', 'ORG'), ('SymptomsIf', 'ORG'), ('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('CautionYesPanicNoWith', 'MONEY'), ('Covid-19?The', 'PRODUCT'), ('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('at least 14 days', 'DATE'), ('CentresCollection CentresFind', 'ORG'), ('relative;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;background', 'CARDINAL'), ('flexbox;display', 'CARDINAL'), ('wrap;flex', 'CARDINAL'), ('important;position', 'CARDINAL'), ('relative;-webkit', 'ORG'), ('100ms;transition', 'CARDINAL'), ('100ms;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('#000;font', 'MONEY'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('flex;-webkit-flex:1;-ms', 'PRODUCT'), ('wrap;-ms-flex-wrap', 'PRODUCT'), ('wrap;flex', 'CARDINAL'), ('touch;position', 'CARDINAL'), ('relative;overflow', 'CARDINAL'), ('hidden;box', 'GPE'), ('hidden;position', 'CARDINAL'), ('absolute;text', 'CARDINAL'), ('ellipsis;white', 'CARDINAL'), ('translateY(-50%);-ms', 'ORG'), ('translateY(-50%);box', 'PRODUCT'), ('visible;color', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('flexbox;display', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;background', 'CARDINAL'), ('150ms;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('India Institute of Medical Sciences', 'ORG'), ('Hardinge Medical College', 'ORG'), ('New DelhiLal Path Labs', 'ORG'), ('Block -E', 'ORG'), ('Rohini', 'PERSON'), ('DelhiDr Dangs Lab', 'PERSON'), ('C-2/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Safadarjung Development Area', 'ORG'), ('New-DelhiLaboratory Services', 'ORG'), ('Indraprastha Apollo Hospitals', 'ORG'), ('Sarita Vihar', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Max Lab', 'PERSON'), ('Max Super Speciality Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Saket', 'GPE'), ('Ganga Ram Hospital', 'PERSON'), ('DelhiOncquest Labs Ltd', 'ORG'), ('515', 'CARDINAL'), ('19', 'CARDINAL'), ('DwarkaCity X-Ray & Scan Clinic Pvt Ltd', 'ORG'), ('4B/18', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tilak Nagar', 'PERSON'), ('New DelhiNational Centre for Disease', 'FAC'), ('Manohar Lohia HospitalInstitute', 'PERSON'), ('moreHow', 'PERSON'), ('moreDo', 'CARDINAL'), ('moreCovid-19', 'DATE'), ('diseaseThe', 'PRODUCT'), ('coronavirusThe', 'PRODUCT'), ('Advisory Advisory - Social DistancingDirectives', 'ORG'), ('Novel Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('Testing Guidelines of Indian Council of Medical Research', 'ORG'), ('Passenger Movement', 'ORG'), ('DisembarkationLatest News', 'ORG'), ('CoronavirusIndiaOver 64,000', 'PRODUCT'), ('71.17%India', 'CARDINAL'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('64,553', 'CARDINAL'), ('a day', 'DATE'), ('the health ministry', 'ORG'), ('71.17 per cent', 'MONEY'), ('48,040', 'CARDINAL'), ('1,007', 'CARDINAL'), ('24 hours', 'TIME'), ('8 am', 'TIME'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('2,800', 'CARDINAL'), ('3cr', 'ORDINAL'), ('1.2cr', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('66,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('1,008', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid-19Russia', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Kiran Mazumdar-ShawCoronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('Rahul GandhiCoronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Labs', 'PERSON'), ('FavipiravirBio', 'ORG'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('1,49,460', 'CARDINAL'), ('4,167Delhi', 'CARDINAL'), ('956', 'CARDINAL'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('over 1.49 lakh', 'QUANTITY'), ('4,167', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('deaths1,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('1.45', 'CARDINAL'), ('4,111Covid-19', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Arvind Kejriwal613', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('1,075', 'CARDINAL'), ('1,30,606', 'CARDINAL'), ('AuthoritiesCovid-19', 'ORG'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Satyendra JainPeople', 'ORG'), ('Arvind KejriwalDelhi', 'PERSON'), ('2.0', 'CARDINAL'), ('Today', 'DATE'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('monthly', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE'), ('Satyendar JainBangaloreTotal', 'PERSON'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('KarnatakaThe', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Karnataka', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('6,706', 'CARDINAL'), ('103', 'CARDINAL'), ('3,613.Karnataka', 'CARDINAL'), ('Siddaramaiah', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Karnataka', 'GPE'), ('6,257', 'CARDINAL'), ('KarnatakaBengaluru', 'ORG'), ('Covid doctorsWith BS Yediyurappa', 'FAC'), ('Karnataka CM Siddaramaiah', 'PERSON'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('6,128', 'CARDINAL'), ('KarnatakaKarnataka', 'ORG'), ('Covid-19Bengaluru', 'CARDINAL'), ('Yelahanka', 'LOC'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Vijay Kumar', 'PERSON'), ('Chilkalguda', 'GPE'), ('Hyderabad', 'GPE'), ('June this year', 'DATE'), ('Gandhi General Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('at least 300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid monitoringTelangana CM', 'ORG'), ('Independence DayCovid-19:', 'PRODUCT'), ('1,478', 'CARDINAL'), ('Villagers', 'ORG'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('RMP', 'ORG'), ('Secunderabad Cantt', 'PERSON'), ('Helper App', 'PERSON'), ('Greater Hyderabad Municipal Corporation', 'ORG'), ('zonesTech', 'ORG'), ('210', 'CARDINAL'), ('kin', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Janapriya Nile association', 'ORG'), ('Covid-19Telangana', 'ORG'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('1,550', 'CARDINAL'), ('August', 'DATE'), ('Mamata Banerjee-', 'PERSON'), ('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('August 28', 'DATE'), ('August 20', 'DATE'), ('KolkataAnother', 'ORG'), ('KolkataWest Bengal', 'GPE'), ('40', 'CARDINAL'), ('2,341', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bengal tourism department', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('pandemicSeven-day', 'DATE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('West BengalCovid-19', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('649', 'CARDINAL'), ('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Kolkata', 'GPE'), ('Bengal', 'PERSON'), ('572', 'CARDINAL'), ('11,813', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('413', 'CARDINAL'), ('9,115', 'CARDINAL'), ('11,813', 'CARDINAL'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('5,60,126', 'CARDINAL'), ('413', 'CARDINAL'), ('19,063', 'CARDINAL'), ('the state health department', 'ORG'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('925', 'CARDINAL'), ('46', 'CARDINAL'), ('dieUnlock 3.0', 'ORG'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), (""BR Ambedkar's"", 'ORG'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid-19Mumbai', 'LAW'), ('1,033', 'CARDINAL'), ('39', 'CARDINAL'), ('7,924', 'CARDINAL'), ('227', 'CARDINAL'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('238', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('57', 'CARDINAL'), ('dieMaharashtra', 'ORG'), ('9,431', 'CARDINAL'), (""13,656I'm"", 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Uddhav ThackerayMumbai:', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('36', 'CARDINAL'), ('WorldNew', 'ORG'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('just 20 minutes', 'TIME'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('trialNew Zealand', 'GPE'), ('vaccineUS', 'PRODUCT'), ('supplyUK', 'ORG'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('coming months', 'DATE'), ('next yearPhilippines', 'DATE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('OctoberSpeaking Tree StoriesChronicle', 'ORG'), ('Arthur Conan Doyle’s', 'PERSON'), ('The Poison Belt', 'FAC'), ('Challenger', 'PERSON'), ('introspectionCorona Karma?Corona', 'PERSON'), ('ahimsaWe’re', 'PERSON'), ('fareShh', 'PERSON'), ('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('WHO01:35Indore', 'PERSON'), ('3,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bihar', 'PERSON'), ('Indians', 'NORP'), ('Health Pharmacies', 'ORG'), ('Punjab01:32Govt', 'GPE'), ('Aarogya Setu', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('last 24 hours', 'TIME'), ('31.15%', 'PERCENT'), ('Indians', 'NORP'), ('5 lakh migrants', 'QUANTITY'), ('500', 'CARDINAL'), ('3.0', 'CARDINAL'), ('ChennaiMore Updates', 'ORG'), ('CoronavirusLive', 'ORG'), ('49,310', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('CovidCan', 'ORG'), ('India & worldIndia', 'ORG'), ('one million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Arvind Kejriwal', 'PERSON'), ('PMICMR nod', 'PERSON'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('nearly 3k', 'CARDINAL'), ('MahaCovid', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('37,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('1,25,101Covid-19', 'CARDINAL'), ('over 5,200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('0.2', 'CARDINAL'), (""Trump ultimatum'Migrants"", 'ORG'), ('200', 'CARDINAL'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('December 2019', 'DATE'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('dozen', 'CARDINAL'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('weeks', 'DATE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('United States', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('billions of dollars', 'MONEY'), ('a few weeks', 'DATE'), ('sitesThe Economic TimesHindi Economic', 'ORG'), ('GujaratTimes NowTimes', 'PERSON'), ('Gold PodcastEi', 'PERSON'), ('entertainmentMensXP.comFeminaETimesGraziaZoomTravel DestinationsBombay', 'ORG'), ('PrimeWhats Hottop', 'PRODUCT'), ('IndiaKamala HarrisPranab MukherjeeCoronavirus India', 'PRODUCT'), ('PilotPranab Mukherjee', 'ORG'), ('InflationFinal Year Exam NewsCBSE', 'EVENT'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('NextAstro SpeakGadgets', 'PRODUCT'), ('NewsBusiness NewsIndia NewsWorld NewsBollywood NewsHealth & Fitness', 'ORG'), ('TipsIndian', 'NORP'), ('Case Live UpdatesSSR', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('ManagerSanjay', 'ORG'), ('NieceSushant SisterAlia BhattSanjana SanghiTrending topicsDisha', 'PRODUCT'), ('PataniBollywood', 'ORG'), ('CousinSushant FamilyKareena KapoorOxford Coronavirus VaccineAmazon', 'PRODUCT'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('SaleCoronavirus', 'ORG'), ('MumbaiFollow', 'ORG'), ('RSS Sitemap Archives', 'ORG'), ('Bennett, Coleman &', 'ORG'), ('Times Syndication Service', 'ORG')]"
96,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,"Englishहिन्दीमराठीবাংলা ગુજરાતીಕನ್ನಡதமிழ்తెలుగుമലയാളം|Epaper|GadgetsNowSign InTOITOICoronavirusBriefsWorldBusinessSportsEntertainmentTVLifestylePhotosEducationPoliticsElectionsCoronavirusHas curve flattened?India Lockdown: FAQsPreventionTreatmentSymptomsIndiaDelhiBangaloreHyderabadKolkataMumbaiWorldCovid-19 FAQsSpeaking TreeNews HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCouponsNewsCoronaviruscovid-19 casesIndiaWorldview on mapSource: MOHFW(India) and John HopkinsDailyCumulative.css-2b097c-container{position:relative;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-8rldbw-control{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;background-color:hsl(0,0%,100%);border-color:hsl(0,0%,80%);border-radius:0px;border-style:solid;border-width:0;cursor:default;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex-wrap:wrap;-ms-flex-wrap:wrap;flex-wrap:wrap;-webkit-box-pack:justify;-webkit-justify-content:space-between;-ms-flex-pack:justify;justify-content:space-between;min-height:38px;outline:0 !important;position:relative;-webkit-transition:all 100ms;transition:all 100ms;box-sizing:border-box;border-bottom:1px solid #000;font-size:16px;font-weight:600;}.css-8rldbw-control:hover{border-color:hsl(0,0%,70%);}.css-1hwfws3{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex:1;-ms-flex:1;flex:1;-webkit-flex-wrap:wrap;-ms-flex-wrap:wrap;flex-wrap:wrap;padding:2px 8px;-webkit-overflow-scrolling:touch;position:relative;overflow:hidden;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-12jugfk-placeholder{color:#999;margin-left:2px;margin-right:2px;position:absolute;top:50%;-webkit-transform:translateY(-50%);-ms-transform:translateY(-50%);transform:translateY(-50%);box-sizing:border-box;font-size:14px;font-weight:600;}Select State/UT.css-1g6gooi{margin:2px;padding-bottom:2px;padding-top:2px;visibility:visible;color:hsl(0,0%,20%);box-sizing:border-box;}.css-1wy0on6{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-align-self:stretch;-ms-flex-item-align:stretch;align-self:stretch;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex-shrink:0;-ms-flex-negative:0;flex-shrink:0;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-43ykx9-indicatorSeparator{-webkit-align-self:stretch;-ms-flex-item-align:stretch;align-self:stretch;background-color:hsl(0,0%,80%);margin-bottom:8px;margin-top:8px;width:1px;box-sizing:border-box;display:none;}.css-h0ri03-indicatorContainer{color:hsl(0,0%,80%);display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;padding:8px;-webkit-transition:color 150ms;transition:color 150ms;box-sizing:border-box;background-image:url(https://static.toiimg.com/photo/74612995.cms);background-repeat:no-repeat;background-position:-13px -227px;}.css-h0ri03-indicatorContainer:hover{color:hsl(0,0%,60%);}.css-19bqh2r{display:inline-block;fill:currentColor;line-height:1;stroke:currentColor;stroke-width:0;}Has the curve flattened?Find OutCovid-19 India StatusBy State/UTBy DistrictPreventive MeasuresPrecautions we suggest: Wash hands frequently, avoid crowded places...read moreCoronavirus SymptomsIf you have a fever, cough and difficulty breathing...read moreMyths vs RealityBe aware! The most pervasive myths on Coronavirus and why they are wrong.read moreLive Updates Coronavirus live updates: India's Covid tally now over 24 lakh, deaths cross 48,000-markQ&A ON CORONAVIRUS (COVID-19) #CautionYesPanicNoWith inputs from:How is one tested for Covid-19?The test for coronavirus does not involve any blood examination. Coronavirus test includes examining of the throat swab or the nasal swab to check for infection. After taking samples, doctors posted at nodal hospitals may assess your physical health to decide whether hospitalisation is needed. Otherwise, you may be asked to stay isolated at home itself. If the tests are positive, you may require to remain quarantined for at least 14 days, till recovery.What should you do if you want to get tested for Covid-19 in India?If you get infected with COVID-19 and recover, can you get infected again?Can higher immunity prevent you from getting coronavirus?Should I wear a mask?more questions and answersTesting CentresCollection CentresFind COVID-19 testing centres near you.css-2b097c-container{position:relative;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-8rldbw-control{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;background-color:hsl(0,0%,100%);border-color:hsl(0,0%,80%);border-radius:0px;border-style:solid;border-width:0;cursor:default;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex-wrap:wrap;-ms-flex-wrap:wrap;flex-wrap:wrap;-webkit-box-pack:justify;-webkit-justify-content:space-between;-ms-flex-pack:justify;justify-content:space-between;min-height:38px;outline:0 !important;position:relative;-webkit-transition:all 100ms;transition:all 100ms;box-sizing:border-box;border-bottom:1px solid #000;font-size:16px;font-weight:600;}.css-8rldbw-control:hover{border-color:hsl(0,0%,70%);}.css-1hwfws3{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex:1;-ms-flex:1;flex:1;-webkit-flex-wrap:wrap;-ms-flex-wrap:wrap;flex-wrap:wrap;padding:2px 8px;-webkit-overflow-scrolling:touch;position:relative;overflow:hidden;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-1wh03ml-singleValue{color:#000;margin-left:2px;margin-right:2px;max-width:calc(100% - 8px);overflow:hidden;position:absolute;text-overflow:ellipsis;white-space:nowrap;top:50%;-webkit-transform:translateY(-50%);-ms-transform:translateY(-50%);transform:translateY(-50%);box-sizing:border-box;}Delhi.css-1g6gooi{margin:2px;padding-bottom:2px;padding-top:2px;visibility:visible;color:hsl(0,0%,20%);box-sizing:border-box;}.css-1wy0on6{-webkit-align-items:center;-webkit-box-align:center;-ms-flex-align:center;align-items:center;-webkit-align-self:stretch;-ms-flex-item-align:stretch;align-self:stretch;display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;-webkit-flex-shrink:0;-ms-flex-negative:0;flex-shrink:0;box-sizing:border-box;}.css-43ykx9-indicatorSeparator{-webkit-align-self:stretch;-ms-flex-item-align:stretch;align-self:stretch;background-color:hsl(0,0%,80%);margin-bottom:8px;margin-top:8px;width:1px;box-sizing:border-box;display:none;}.css-h0ri03-indicatorContainer{color:hsl(0,0%,80%);display:-webkit-box;display:-webkit-flex;display:-ms-flexbox;display:flex;padding:8px;-webkit-transition:color 150ms;transition:color 150ms;box-sizing:border-box;background-image:url(https://static.toiimg.com/photo/74612995.cms);background-repeat:no-repeat;background-position:-13px -227px;}.css-h0ri03-indicatorContainer:hover{color:hsl(0,0%,60%);}.css-19bqh2r{display:inline-block;fill:currentColor;line-height:1;stroke:currentColor;stroke-width:0;}All India Institute of Medical Sciences, New Delhi- 110029Lady Hardinge Medical College, New DelhiLal Path Labs, Block -E, Sector 18, Rohini, DelhiDr Dangs Lab, C-2/1, Safadarjung Development Area, New-DelhiLaboratory Services, Indraprastha Apollo Hospitals, Sarita Vihar, New Delhi Max Lab, Max Super Speciality Hospital, Saket, New-DelhiSir Ganga Ram Hospital Clinical Lab Services, Sir Ganga Ram Hospital, DelhiOncquest Labs Ltd, 3-Factory Road, New-DelhiPrognosis Laboratories, 515-16, Sector 19, DwarkaCity X-Ray & Scan Clinic Pvt Ltd, 4B/18, Tilak Nagar, New DelhiNational Centre for Disease ControlRam Manohar Lohia HospitalInstitute of Liver & Biliary SciencesArmy Hospital Research & ReferralNote: No. of testing labs and collection centres are increasing. We will keep updating it as and when we get more information.Quick TipsLockdown: What's open?know moreHow to Self Quarantine?know moreDo's and Dont's for Covid-19know moreCovid-19 or flu? How to find out?know moreMost Rampant Myths on Covid-19 #CautionYesPanicNoSpraying alcohol or chlorine all over your body kill the coronavirusEating garlic can treat coronavirusCold weather and snow kill the new coronavirusTaking a hot bath prevents the new coronavirus diseaseThe new coronavirus can be transmitted through a mosquito biteHand dryers are effective in killing the new coronavirusPets at home can spread the new coronavirusThe virus only affects older peopleread full listGovernment Advisory Advisory - Social DistancingDirectives from MoHRD for all Educational Institutions and Examination Boards regarding precautions to be taken in light of COVID-19DoPT OM - Preventive measures to be taken to contain the spread of Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19)Latest Testing Guidelines of Indian Council of Medical Research (ICMR)Guidelines for notifying COVID-19 affected persons by Private InstitutionsStandard Operating Procedure for Passenger Movement post DisembarkationLatest News from CoronavirusIndiaOver 64,000 fresh Covid-19 cases; recovery rate improves to 71.17%India's Covid-19 caseload surpassed 24 lakh on Friday after 64,553 people tested positive in a day, and the recoveries rose to over 17 lakh, the health ministry said. With 17,51,555 people defeating the disease, the recovery rate has surged to 71.17 per cent. The caseload increased to 24,61,190, while the death toll climbed to 48,040 with 1,007 people succumbing to the disease in 24 hours, the ministry data updated at 8 am showed.US, China to discuss trade deal amid Covid-19 disruptionZydus' 'budget' injection costs 2,800/shotCentre distributed 3cr masks, 1.2cr PPEsIn biggest Covid surge, 66,000+ cases, 1,008 deaths in one dayWHO chief scientist bats for focus on contact tracing, testing in fight against Covid-19Russia not world's first to develop coronavirus vaccine: Kiran Mazumdar-ShawCoronavirus curve 'frightening, not flattening': Rahul GandhiCoronavirus roundup: Developments in India and rest of worldMSN Labs rolls out cheapest Covid-19 drug FavipiravirBio E in pact with J&J to manufacture Covid-19 vaccineDelhi956 new Covid-19 cases take Delhi tally to 1,49,460; death toll climbs to 4,167Delhi recorded 956 fresh coronavirus cases on Thursday, raising the city's infection tally to over 1.49 lakh, while the death toll from the disease mounted to 4,167, authorities said.1,113 more Covid-19 cases in Delhi; 14 more deaths1,300 new cases take Delhi's Covid-19 caseload to over 1.45 lakh; toll climbs to 4,111Covid-19 situation in Delhi under control: Arvind Kejriwal613 new Covid-19 cases in Delhi; toll 3853Delhi records 1,075 fresh Covid-19 cases; tally rises to 1,30,606: AuthoritiesCovid-19 'situation satisfactory' in Delhi: Satyendra JainPeople, govts together attained victory over Covid-19, fight not yet over: Arvind KejriwalDelhi unlock 2.0 news: Today's updatesRecovered Delhi cop tests positive again, raises question if coronavirus can reinfectDelhi govt plans more monthly sero-surveys, next to be done in August: Satyendar JainBangaloreTotal number of Covid-19 infections breach 2 lakh-mark in KarnatakaThe number of Covid-19 infections breached the 2 lakh mark in Karnataka on Thursday as the state reported 6,706 new cases of coronavirus and 103 related fatalities, taking the death toll to 3,613.Karnataka: Siddaramaiah discharged after testing negative for Covid-19Over one lakh Covid patients discharged so far in Karnataka, 6,257 new infectionsPrompt hospital admission after positive antigen test: BBMPCovid-19: Health teams to test vulnerable citizens across KarnatakaBengaluru: Volunteer group serves food to city Covid doctorsWith BS Yediyurappa in hospital, cabinet reshuffle, policies hang fireFormer Karnataka CM Siddaramaiah tests positive for Covid, admitted to hospitalBiggest single-day spike of 6,128 new Covid-19 cases in KarnatakaKarnataka forest minister tests positive for Covid-19Bengaluru: Collective effort helped Yelahanka apartment stay safeHyderabadHyderabad: Cop donates plasma for Covid-positive doctor, who treated 300 coronavirus patientsConstable E Vijay Kumar from Chilkalguda police station in Hyderabad, who contracted coronavirus in June this year while performing his duties as front-line worker at Gandhi General Hospital, on Thursday donated his plasma to save the life of a senior doctor, who has treated at least 300 Covid-19 patients, before he himself contracted the infection.Health minister inaugurates special buses for Covid monitoringTelangana CM directs release of prisoners with good conduct on occasion of Independence DayCovid-19: Telangana toll tops 400-mark , state records 1,478 new infectionsTelangana: Villagers protest burial of Covid victim RMP doctorPeople make a beeline for free Covid-19 test at Secunderabad Cantt BoardCO Helper App to provide info on Covid-19 beds, ambulancesCovid-19: Greater Hyderabad Municipal Corporation redefines containment zonesTech Mahindra charters flight to bring 210 staffers, kin in US homeHyderabad: Janapriya Nile association gets its act together to fight Covid-19Telangana registers 9 Covid-19 deaths, 1,550 new infectionsKolkataWest Bengal govt withdraws state-wide lockdown on August 28The Mamata Banerjee-led West Bengal government on Wednesday withdrew the complete lockdown on August 28 and imposed a curfew on August 20 instead.Traffic cop succumbs to Covid-19 in KolkataAnother senior doctor dies of Covid-19 in KolkataWest Bengal reports 40 new Covid-19 deaths, 2,341 fresh casesKolkata police sensitise people about bi-weekly lockdownWest Bengal tourism department reopens 10 facilities amid Covid-19 pandemicSeven-day lockdown imposed from 5pm in all containment zones of West BengalCovid-19 claims 16 more lives in West Bengal; 649 fresh casesMamata Banerjee extends free ration scheme of West Bengal govt till June 2021Commuter hassles aggravate in Kolkata as several private buses stay off roads citing lossesWest Bengal reports highest single-day spike of 572 Covid-19 cases; tally crosses 17,000-markMumbaiMaharashtra: 11,813 new Covid cases, 413 deaths, 9,115 recoveriesMaharashtra registered a spike of 11,813 new cases on Thursday which took the coronavirus tally in the state to 5,60,126. With 413 Covid-19 patients dying, the death toll in the state reached 19,063, the state health department said.Mumbai reports 925 new Covid-19 cases, 46 more dieUnlock 3.0 in Mumbai: Coronavirus cases update and latest news from your cityVandalism at BR Ambedkar's Mumbai house: Two suspects test positive for Covid-19Mumbai reports 1,033 new Covid-19 cases, 39 deathsMaharashtra reports 7,924 fresh Covid-19 cases, 227 deathsMumbai: Dharavi adds 9 new Covid-19 cases; doubling rate over 238 days1,115 new Covid-19 cases detected in Mumbai; 57 more dieMaharashtra's Covid-19 count grows by 9,431; death toll now 13,656I'm not ready to let people die by lifting lockdown in one go: Uddhav ThackerayMumbai: Dharavi reports 36 new Covid-19 casesRest of the WorldNew low-cost test can diagnose Covid-19 in just 20 minutesMELBOURNE: Scientists have developed a new low-cost nasal swab test which can accurately diagnose the presence of SARS-CoV-2 virus that causes Covid-19 in just 20 minutes.WHO in conversation with Russia for more vaccine information: expertIndonesia takes part in late-stage China vaccine trialNew Zealand probing for outbreak source, may expand lockdownBiological E to make substance used in J&J's potential Covid-19 vaccineUS recruits scientists abroad for Covid-19 vaccine trials, pledges access to supplyUK begins testing a new app to fight Covid-19 spreadFinland reverses policy, recommends mask useScientists identify hundreds of drugs to treat Covid-19Germany: Optimistic we'll have a vaccine in coming months and certainly next yearPhilippines eyes clinical trials for Russian Covid-19 vaccine in OctoberSpeaking Tree StoriesChronicle of a pandemic foretoldPerhaps one of the earliest fictional accounts of a global threat that wipes out all forms of life is Arthur Conan Doyle’s The Poison Belt, which features the scientific genius, Professor Challenger, and was written in 1913.How to connect despite physical distancingIs your cough infectious?New doorway to introspectionCorona Karma?Corona is here, but where is karuna?Fearlessness  and ahimsaWe’re part of the wholeTake this quiz and see how you fareShh be still, be calmProtect yourself from the fear contagion Video updates on Coronavirus 01:13Spraying disinfectants on streets can be 'harmful': WHO01:13Spraying disinfectants on streets can be 'harmful': WHO01:35Indore: Migrant workers, stranded students sent to Rewa by special train01:03Noida: 3,000 migrant workers travel to Bihar onboard special trains01:54Heartwarming messages from stranded Indians as they board repatriation flight from Dhaka01:52Rural Health Pharmacies employees protest over salary hike in Punjab01:32Govt rubbishes privacy concerns in Aarogya Setu, says app designed with ‘privacy-first’ measure01:194,213 COVID-19 cases in last 24 hours, recovery rate improved to 31.15%: Centre01:104000 Indians brought back by flights, 5 lakh migrants went home via trains: Centre03:23COVID-19: GCC Biotech lab prepares ‘real-time’ test kits worth Rs 500 in WB01:07Lockdown 3.0: Standalone outlets reopen in ChennaiMore Updates from CoronavirusLive: Biggest single-day spike of 49,310 casesIndia, Israel to develop rapid testing for CovidCan you get Covid again? It’s unlikely, experts say  Covid-19 roundup: Developments in India & worldIndia needs one million tests daily: CCMB chiefCM Arvind Kejriwal rules out another lockdownCoronavirus vaccine update: All you need to knowLive: Signs of economic recovery visible, says PMICMR nod for antigen-based testing kit for faster diagnosis6,300+ new Covid cases, nearly 3k from MahaCovid: Economist warns of 10 yrs of depression‘Lockdown prevented 37,000-78,000 deaths’Covid live: Total cases in India rise to 1,25,101Covid-19: Home loan rates set to dip, EMIs to fallIndia records over 5,200 Covid cases in a dayCovid-19: India reports 0.2 deaths per lakhDental clinics: Only urgent cases allowedWHO faces virus probe after Trump ultimatum'Migrants to be tracked, focus on keeping toll low'Railways to run 200 non-AC trains daily from June 1The first case of coronavirus was reported in December 2019 in the Wuhan city of China as a pneumonia outbreak. Later, its root was traced to a novel strain of coronavirus. The outbreak of coronavirus infection soon spread to other provinces of the country, forcing the govt to lockdown dozen of cities with millions of people. Within weeks, the coronavirus spread outside of the country to other nations like South Korea, Iran, Italy, United States, India, Pakistan among others.  The number of positive cases of novel coronavirus infection is increasing day-by-day all across the globe. Countries around the world have taken strict decisions to close the entry of foreigners, schools, colleges, gyms, clubs, cinema halls, malls and other public places to stop the spread of Covid-19. The novel coronavirus also knocked down the global financial markets with billions of dollars being wiped off in a matter of a few weeks.Get the appback to topOther Times Group news sitesThe Economic TimesHindi Economic TimesNavbharat TimesMaharashtra TimesVijaya KarnatakaTelugu SamayamTamil SamayamMalayalam SamayamEi SamayI am GujaratTimes NowTimes Now HindiTimesPointsIndiatimesBrand CapitalEducation TimesTimes FoodMiss KyraMumbai MirrorPune MirrorAhmedabad MirrorBangalore MirrorMX PlayerNBT Gold PodcastEi Samay Gold PodcastMX ShareKaroMX TakaTak AppLiving and entertainmentMensXP.comFeminaETimesGraziaZoomTravel DestinationsBombay TimesCricbuzz.comFilmfareOnline SongsTVLifestyle Longwalks AppNewspaper SubscriptionFood NewsTimes PrimeWhats Hottop trendsCoronavirus cases in IndiaKamala HarrisPranab MukherjeeCoronavirus India update liveSachin PilotPranab Mukherjee newsRajasthan newsRetail InflationFinal Year Exam NewsCBSE Compartment ExamH1B VisaComedk Exam NewsNewsFinal Year Exam NewsCoronavirus newsHoroscope todayLatest newsStep by Step Pizza RecipeservicesAds 2 BookBank Exam AppET Money Finance AppCouponDuniaDineoutMagicbricksTechgigTimes JobsBollywood NewsTimes MobileRemit 2 IndiaTC NextAstro SpeakGadgets NowCareersColombiaPopular CategoriesHeadlinesSports NewsBusiness NewsIndia NewsWorld NewsBollywood NewsHealth & Fitness TipsIndian TV ShowsCelebrity Photoshot on the webKareena Kapoor KhanSSR CaseSSR Case Live UpdatesSSR Former ManagerSanjay DuttSSR NieceSushant SisterAlia BhattSanjana SanghiTrending topicsDisha PataniBollywood CelebsNiharika KonidelaMouni RoyCentre on SSR CaseVijay FanShweta Video AppealIbrahim Ali KhanSanjay Dutt's CousinSushant FamilyKareena KapoorOxford Coronavirus VaccineAmazon App QuizJio Janmashtami OfferMoto Razr 5G 2020Vivo Y1sAmazon SaleCoronavirus in MumbaiFollow us onfacebooktwitterrss feedyoutubedownload toi appandroidiphoneBlackBerryipadwindows phoneText resize:aaaAbout us Create Your Own Ad Terms of Use and Grievance Redressal Policy Privacy policy Advertise with us RSS Sitemap Archives Copyright © 2020 Bennett, Coleman & Co. Ltd. All rights reserved. For reprint rights: Times Syndication Service","[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG'), ('EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe', 'PRODUCT'), ('mapSource', 'ORG'), ('John HopkinsDailyCumulative.css-2b097c-container{position', 'PERSON'), ('relative;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;background', 'CARDINAL'), ('flexbox;display', 'CARDINAL'), ('wrap;flex', 'CARDINAL'), ('important;position', 'CARDINAL'), ('relative;-webkit', 'ORG'), ('100ms;transition', 'CARDINAL'), ('100ms;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('#000;font', 'MONEY'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('flex;-webkit-flex:1;-ms', 'PRODUCT'), ('wrap;-ms-flex-wrap', 'PRODUCT'), ('wrap;flex', 'CARDINAL'), ('touch;position', 'CARDINAL'), ('relative;overflow', 'CARDINAL'), ('hidden;box', 'GPE'), ('translateY(-50%);-ms', 'PERSON'), ('translateY(-50%);box', 'PRODUCT'), ('visible;color', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('flexbox;display', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;background', 'CARDINAL'), ('150ms;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('DistrictPreventive MeasuresPrecautions', 'ORG'), ('SymptomsIf', 'ORG'), ('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('CautionYesPanicNoWith', 'MONEY'), ('Covid-19?The', 'PRODUCT'), ('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('at least 14 days', 'DATE'), ('CentresCollection CentresFind', 'ORG'), ('relative;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;background', 'CARDINAL'), ('flexbox;display', 'CARDINAL'), ('wrap;flex', 'CARDINAL'), ('important;position', 'CARDINAL'), ('relative;-webkit', 'ORG'), ('100ms;transition', 'CARDINAL'), ('100ms;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('#000;font', 'MONEY'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('flex;-webkit-flex:1;-ms', 'PRODUCT'), ('wrap;-ms-flex-wrap', 'PRODUCT'), ('wrap;flex', 'CARDINAL'), ('touch;position', 'CARDINAL'), ('relative;overflow', 'CARDINAL'), ('hidden;box', 'GPE'), ('hidden;position', 'CARDINAL'), ('absolute;text', 'CARDINAL'), ('ellipsis;white', 'CARDINAL'), ('translateY(-50%);-ms', 'ORG'), ('translateY(-50%);box', 'PRODUCT'), ('visible;color', 'CARDINAL'), ('center;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('flexbox;display', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;align', 'CARDINAL'), ('stretch;background', 'CARDINAL'), ('150ms;box', 'CARDINAL'), ('India Institute of Medical Sciences', 'ORG'), ('Hardinge Medical College', 'ORG'), ('New DelhiLal Path Labs', 'ORG'), ('Block -E', 'ORG'), ('Rohini', 'PERSON'), ('DelhiDr Dangs Lab', 'PERSON'), ('C-2/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Safadarjung Development Area', 'ORG'), ('New-DelhiLaboratory Services', 'ORG'), ('Indraprastha Apollo Hospitals', 'ORG'), ('Sarita Vihar', 'PERSON'), ('New Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Max Lab', 'PERSON'), ('Max Super Speciality Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Saket', 'GPE'), ('Ganga Ram Hospital', 'PERSON'), ('DelhiOncquest Labs Ltd', 'ORG'), ('515', 'CARDINAL'), ('19', 'CARDINAL'), ('DwarkaCity X-Ray & Scan Clinic Pvt Ltd', 'ORG'), ('4B/18', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tilak Nagar', 'PERSON'), ('New DelhiNational Centre for Disease', 'FAC'), ('Manohar Lohia HospitalInstitute', 'PERSON'), ('moreHow', 'PERSON'), ('moreDo', 'CARDINAL'), ('moreCovid-19', 'DATE'), ('diseaseThe', 'PRODUCT'), ('coronavirusThe', 'PRODUCT'), ('Advisory Advisory - Social DistancingDirectives', 'ORG'), ('Novel Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('Testing Guidelines of Indian Council of Medical Research', 'ORG'), ('Passenger Movement', 'ORG'), ('DisembarkationLatest News', 'ORG'), ('CoronavirusIndiaOver 64,000', 'PRODUCT'), ('71.17%India', 'CARDINAL'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('64,553', 'CARDINAL'), ('a day', 'DATE'), ('the health ministry', 'ORG'), ('71.17 per cent', 'MONEY'), ('48,040', 'CARDINAL'), ('1,007', 'CARDINAL'), ('24 hours', 'TIME'), ('8 am', 'TIME'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('2,800', 'CARDINAL'), ('3cr', 'ORDINAL'), ('1.2cr', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('66,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('1,008', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid-19Russia', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Kiran Mazumdar-ShawCoronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('Rahul GandhiCoronavirus', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Labs', 'PERSON'), ('FavipiravirBio', 'ORG'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('1,49,460', 'CARDINAL'), ('4,167Delhi', 'CARDINAL'), ('956', 'CARDINAL'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('over 1.49 lakh', 'QUANTITY'), ('4,167', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('deaths1,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('1.45', 'CARDINAL'), ('4,111Covid-19', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Arvind Kejriwal613', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('1,075', 'CARDINAL'), ('1,30,606', 'CARDINAL'), ('AuthoritiesCovid-19', 'ORG'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Satyendra JainPeople', 'ORG'), ('Arvind KejriwalDelhi', 'PERSON'), ('2.0', 'CARDINAL'), ('Today', 'DATE'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('monthly', 'DATE'), ('August', 'DATE'), ('Satyendar JainBangaloreTotal', 'PERSON'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('KarnatakaThe', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Karnataka', 'GPE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('6,706', 'CARDINAL'), ('103', 'CARDINAL'), ('3,613.Karnataka', 'CARDINAL'), ('Siddaramaiah', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Karnataka', 'GPE'), ('6,257', 'CARDINAL'), ('KarnatakaBengaluru', 'ORG'), ('Covid doctorsWith BS Yediyurappa', 'FAC'), ('Karnataka CM Siddaramaiah', 'PERSON'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('6,128', 'CARDINAL'), ('KarnatakaKarnataka', 'ORG'), ('Covid-19Bengaluru', 'CARDINAL'), ('Yelahanka', 'LOC'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Vijay Kumar', 'PERSON'), ('Chilkalguda', 'GPE'), ('Hyderabad', 'GPE'), ('June this year', 'DATE'), ('Gandhi General Hospital', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('at least 300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid monitoringTelangana CM', 'ORG'), ('Independence DayCovid-19:', 'PRODUCT'), ('1,478', 'CARDINAL'), ('Villagers', 'ORG'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('RMP', 'ORG'), ('Secunderabad Cantt', 'PERSON'), ('Helper App', 'PERSON'), ('Greater Hyderabad Municipal Corporation', 'ORG'), ('zonesTech', 'ORG'), ('210', 'CARDINAL'), ('kin', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Janapriya Nile association', 'ORG'), ('Covid-19Telangana', 'ORG'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('1,550', 'CARDINAL'), ('August', 'DATE'), ('Mamata Banerjee-', 'PERSON'), ('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('August 28', 'DATE'), ('August 20', 'DATE'), ('KolkataAnother', 'ORG'), ('KolkataWest Bengal', 'GPE'), ('40', 'CARDINAL'), ('2,341', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bengal tourism department', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('pandemicSeven-day', 'DATE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('West BengalCovid-19', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('649', 'CARDINAL'), ('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Kolkata', 'GPE'), ('Bengal', 'PERSON'), ('572', 'CARDINAL'), ('11,813', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('413', 'CARDINAL'), ('9,115', 'CARDINAL'), ('11,813', 'CARDINAL'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('5,60,126', 'CARDINAL'), ('413', 'CARDINAL'), ('19,063', 'CARDINAL'), ('the state health department', 'ORG'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('925', 'CARDINAL'), ('46', 'CARDINAL'), ('dieUnlock 3.0', 'ORG'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), (""BR Ambedkar's"", 'ORG'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid-19Mumbai', 'LAW'), ('1,033', 'CARDINAL'), ('39', 'CARDINAL'), ('7,924', 'CARDINAL'), ('227', 'CARDINAL'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('238', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('57', 'CARDINAL'), ('dieMaharashtra', 'ORG'), ('9,431', 'CARDINAL'), (""13,656I'm"", 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Uddhav ThackerayMumbai:', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('36', 'CARDINAL'), ('WorldNew', 'ORG'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('just 20 minutes', 'TIME'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('trialNew Zealand', 'GPE'), ('vaccineUS', 'PRODUCT'), ('supplyUK', 'ORG'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('coming months', 'DATE'), ('next yearPhilippines', 'DATE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('OctoberSpeaking Tree StoriesChronicle', 'ORG'), ('Arthur Conan Doyle’s', 'PERSON'), ('The Poison Belt', 'FAC'), ('Challenger', 'PERSON'), ('introspectionCorona Karma?Corona', 'PERSON'), ('ahimsaWe’re', 'PERSON'), ('fareShh', 'PERSON'), ('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('WHO01:35Indore', 'PERSON'), ('3,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bihar', 'PERSON'), ('Indians', 'NORP'), ('Health Pharmacies', 'ORG'), ('Punjab01:32Govt', 'GPE'), ('Aarogya Setu', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('last 24 hours', 'TIME'), ('31.15%', 'PERCENT'), ('Indians', 'NORP'), ('5 lakh migrants', 'QUANTITY'), ('500', 'CARDINAL'), ('3.0', 'CARDINAL'), ('ChennaiMore Updates', 'ORG'), ('CoronavirusLive', 'ORG'), ('49,310', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('CovidCan', 'ORG'), ('India & worldIndia', 'ORG'), ('one million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Arvind Kejriwal', 'PERSON'), ('PMICMR nod', 'PERSON'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('nearly 3k', 'CARDINAL'), ('MahaCovid', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('37,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('1,25,101Covid-19', 'CARDINAL'), ('over 5,200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Covid', 'PRODUCT'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('0.2', 'CARDINAL'), (""Trump ultimatum'Migrants"", 'ORG'), ('200', 'CARDINAL'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('December 2019', 'DATE'), ('Wuhan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('dozen', 'CARDINAL'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('weeks', 'DATE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('United States', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('billions of dollars', 'MONEY'), ('a few weeks', 'DATE'), ('sitesThe Economic TimesHindi Economic', 'ORG'), ('GujaratTimes NowTimes', 'PERSON'), ('Gold PodcastEi', 'PERSON'), ('entertainmentMensXP.comFeminaETimesGraziaZoomTravel DestinationsBombay', 'ORG'), ('PrimeWhats Hottop', 'PRODUCT'), ('IndiaKamala HarrisPranab MukherjeeCoronavirus India', 'PRODUCT'), ('PilotPranab Mukherjee', 'ORG'), ('InflationFinal Year Exam NewsCBSE', 'EVENT'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('NextAstro SpeakGadgets', 'PRODUCT'), ('NewsBusiness NewsIndia NewsWorld NewsBollywood NewsHealth & Fitness', 'ORG'), ('TipsIndian', 'NORP'), ('Case Live UpdatesSSR', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('ManagerSanjay', 'ORG'), ('NieceSushant SisterAlia BhattSanjana SanghiTrending topicsDisha', 'PRODUCT'), ('PataniBollywood', 'ORG'), ('CousinSushant FamilyKareena KapoorOxford Coronavirus VaccineAmazon', 'PRODUCT'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('SaleCoronavirus', 'ORG'), ('MumbaiFollow', 'ORG'), ('RSS Sitemap Archives', 'ORG'), ('Bennett, Coleman &', 'ORG'), ('Times Syndication Service', 'ORG')]"
97,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,Englishहिन्दीमराठीবাংলা ગુજરાતીಕನ್ನಡதமிழ்తెలుగుമലയാളം|Epaper|GadgetsNowSign InTOITOICoronavirusBriefsWorldBusinessSportsEntertainmentTVLifestylePhotosEducationPoliticsElectionsCoronavirusHas curve flattened?India Lockdown: FAQsPreventionTreatmentSymptomsIndiaDelhiBangaloreHyderabadKolkataMumbaiWorldCovid-19 FAQsSpeaking TreeNews HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCouponsNewsCoronavirus,"[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG')]"
98,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,Englishहिन्दीमराठीবাংলা ગુજરાતીಕನ್ನಡதமிழ்తెలుగుമലയാളം|Epaper|GadgetsNowSign InTOITOICoronavirusBriefsWorldBusinessSportsEntertainmentTVLifestylePhotosEducationPoliticsElectionsCoronavirusHas curve flattened?India Lockdown: FAQsPreventionTreatmentSymptomsIndiaDelhiBangaloreHyderabadKolkataMumbaiWorldCovid-19 FAQsSpeaking TreeNews HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCouponsNewsCoronavirus,"[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG')]"
99,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,BriefsWorldBusinessSportsEntertainmentTVLifestylePhotosEducationPoliticsElectionsCoronavirusHas curve flattened?India Lockdown: FAQsPreventionTreatmentSymptomsIndiaDelhiBangaloreHyderabadKolkataMumbaiWorldCovid-19 FAQsSpeaking TreeNews HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCouponsNewsCoronavirus,"[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG')]"
100,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,BriefsWorldBusinessSportsEntertainmentTVLifestylePhotosEducationPoliticsElectionsCoronavirusHas curve flattened?India Lockdown: FAQsPreventionTreatmentSymptomsIndiaDelhiBangaloreHyderabadKolkataMumbaiWorldCovid-19 FAQsSpeaking TreeNews HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCoupons,"[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG')]"
101,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,BriefsWorldBusinessSportsEntertainmentTVLifestylePhotosEducationPoliticsElectionsCoronavirusHas curve flattened?India Lockdown: FAQsPreventionTreatmentSymptomsIndiaDelhiBangaloreHyderabadKolkataMumbaiWorldCovid-19 FAQsSpeaking TreeNews HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCoupons,"[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG')]"
102,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,BriefsWorldBusinessSportsEntertainmentTVLifestylePhotosEducationPoliticsElectionsCoronavirusHas curve flattened?India Lockdown: FAQsPreventionTreatmentSymptomsIndiaDelhiBangaloreHyderabadKolkataMumbaiWorldCovid-19 FAQsSpeaking TreeNews HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCoupons,"[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG')]"
103,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,BriefsWorldBusinessSportsEntertainmentTVLifestylePhotosEducationPoliticsElectionsCoronavirusHas curve flattened?India Lockdown: FAQsPreventionTreatmentSymptomsIndiaDelhiBangaloreHyderabadKolkataMumbaiWorldCovid-19 FAQsSpeaking TreeNews HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCoupons,"[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG')]"
104,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,BriefsWorldBusinessSportsEntertainmentTVLifestylePhotosEducationPoliticsElectionsCoronavirusHas curve flattened?India Lockdown: FAQsPreventionTreatmentSymptomsIndiaDelhiBangaloreHyderabadKolkataMumbaiWorldCovid-19 FAQsSpeaking Tree,[]
105,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,News HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCoupons,"[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG')]"
106,TOI,https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/coronavirus,News HomeCitySmart CitiesIndiaElections 2020PoliticsWorldCitizen ReporterNRIPollutionHeadlinesPodcastsSunday TimesGood NewsTOI FeaturesSpecialsTimes Fact CheckGood GovernanceEditorialsTOI EditorialsET EditorialsEntertainmentMovie ReviewsPhotos (ETIMES)MusicBeauty PageantsEventsFilmfareVideosLive TVTVTV NewsTV ListingsTimes NowET NowZoom TVBusinessStartupsIndia BusinessInternational BusinessLifestyleFeminaWomenAutoTravelRecipesSportsCricketIPLFootballTOISANewMost Searched ProductsElectronicsFashionBeautyHealth & FitnessToday's DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest NewsTech PhotosLatest GadgetsReviewsCompare GadgetsGadgets NewsServicesMediawireEpaperNewspaper SubscriptionReal EstateLaunchpadClassifiedsArchivesPropertyBe SwatantraCoupons,"[('2020PoliticsWorldCitizen', 'CARDINAL'), ('TimesGood', 'ORG'), ('ReviewsPhotos', 'ORG'), ('DealsFood & BeveragesHome Decor & GardenOpinionInfographicsHumourCartoonsCampaignsBlogsSocialViral NewsTrending NewsEducationEducation FestEnvironmentBennett UniversityTOI', 'ORG'), ('StudentTimes Study AbroadJobsAstrologyHoroscopePlanets & TransitsRituals & PujaTechnologyLatest', 'ORG'), ('NewsTech PhotosLatest', 'ORG'), ('GadgetsGadgets', 'ORG'), ('SubscriptionReal', 'ORG')]"
